There's a bazaar at Yomogi Nursery!
Be sure to come by!
Squishy?
Wait, is that you, Ioryogi?
Who else looks like this?
Of course it's me!
How long are you gonna keep your hand there?
Sorry...
Koba-
Ioryogi?
Ioryogi!
Were you napping in town?
If you're tired, you should go home and rest in bed.
I wasn't napping!
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Mysterious Life-form.
Did something happen to you, Ioryogi?
What do you mean, "something"!?
Can't you tell just by looking at me?
Well...
Umm...
You're all muddy!
Guess again!
Anyway, shut up and listen!
It's gotten pretty cloudy.
It's okay.
I'm sure it will clear up.
That'd be nice.
Ioryogi?
I'm gonna go get something that's sure to sell.
Thanks!
Now of course, no way I'd really do that.
I'm sick and tired of hanging around the nursery acting like a stuffed animal.
I'm gonna go see that bear and get myself some baumkuchen.
Man, he always puts it in such weird places.
One long!
Okay!
Four slices!
Bear's Baumkuchery
Happy Hour
Is the short one done yet?
One slice, please!
Slices for a party of three are done!
Is mine done yet?
Hold on a sec, it's cooking!
Six slices done!
How about the long?
Hold on!
Two more minutes!
Looks like you're doing pretty well.
It was Zuisho's idea.
Not bad.
We're going to try variations, too. Like a chocolate one.
Doesn't sound half bad.
Let's give it a try.
You two sure are getting along well.
I wasn't sure at first, but it seems to be going great.
You couldn't even tell I was being sarcastic.
Oh, never mind.
That's right! We deliver now, too!
Here.
Oh, you're from the Bear's Baumkuchery?
I've been waiting. Thanks.
Don't worry about it.
Huh, you're not the bird like usual. Did you just start?
No.
Oh, you're just part-time?
I used to have a part-time job.
My boss sent me all over.
Is that all?
Later.
Hold on!
One time I went to this place, almost like a labyrinth, full of strange rooms.
On Break
You're so caught up in this that I can't even remember what you used to be like.
Nothing wrong with this body.
It's a bit hairy, if I put my mind to it I can do anything.
It's scary how used to it I am. I feel like I've been this way my whole life.
It all seems like a dream now.
More like a nightmare for us.
It feels like it's been such a long time.
Yeah.
If you actually think it through, there's no way we could have won.
We bit off more than we could chew.
Like trying to arm-wrestle an octopus.
We lost so quick.
I kind of remember throwing someone overboard trying to save myself, but...
It was me.
It was you, Ginko!? Sorry!
What's done is done.
I don't have time now to get riled up over that.
Man, we sure were-
That's enough.
Even if you hadn't gone along with it, the rules are the rules.
All I can do now is keep cooking my baumkuchen and wait for things to cool down.
Yeah.
I still have my regrets.
There's nothing to regret!
I object!
Don't even think anything that terrible!
That's right! Next time we make it to Heaven, we're not gonna end up as bears and birds!
I'll be a teddy bear! And he'll end up as birdseed!
No way!
Why do you get to be the cute one?
Anyway, just don't cause any more trouble.
Okay?
Wait, huh?
Don't eat that! That's my inventory!
Man, he only gave me one box to take home. What a stingy bear.
All right.
Hm, after sweets maybe I should have something salty.
And then after that, more of this baumkuchen.
I don't have anything, though.
Soy would be fine too, but right now I'm in the mood for salty.
Man, my stomach's growling.
What are you doing?
Sorry, I missed.
Huh, the ball came back.
That's funny.
Damn brats.
What's so fun about kicking a ball around?
What the hell is this!?
What's going on?
Hey, stop it!
I'm not your dinner!
These are mine!
No baumkuchen for you!
Now knock it off or I'll roast you!
Hey!
Come on! Stop it!
I'm-not-giving-you-this-even-if-I-die!
What!?
Oh no, not water.
I'm getting worn out...
I feel like I'm gonna hork up more than just fire...
There!
My body feels so heavy...
Man, when it rains, it pours.
I can dry right out in one of those.
Dryers are tougher than I thought...
Wait, where am I?
Really?
Yeah, that grocer...
Man, I'm hungry.
No! I'm gonna take my time and enjoy it after I get home!
I'm not a little kid, I can wait until I'm done. ... Maybe.
No, no, no!
This tasty smell...
What's that mysterious life-form?
Welcome to Mocona Land!
Young ladies and gentlemen, don't have so much fun that you get lost!
But be sure to have lots of fun!
I sure have ended up somewhere weird.
Oh, right! That smell...
They all seem so tasty!
Oww...
Oh man...
Excuse me...
Eh? Hey, hold it!
Excuse me!
Dammit, I may be a stuffed animal now, but I'm not really...
If I don't get out of here quick, someone's gonna take my baumkuchen!
Wait, where's this?
What's he doing?
I'll get whichever one you want!
Wait, don't tell me-
Papa, I want that one!
All right!
This is-!
A shooting range!?
Here.
Nice!
Papa, I want the blue doggie!
Hm...
Hmm...
That one, right?
Me!?
Aww.
Whoops, I missed.
That's nothing to laugh about!
All right, this time I'll get him!
Oh no! It's coming straight at me!
You missed again!
Boo.
Huh, that's weird. Okay, this time for sure!
Wait, did it move?
It didn't move, you just can't aim.
Man, now you've got me riled up.
Do your best!
All right! I'll get it!
How about this time?
Dammit, grow up! Stop being so stubborn!
All right!
I'll try too!
We'll help out!
This is horrible!
He sure is hard to hit.
Leave it to me!
I may look like this now, but they used to call me "Kana the Sniper".
Who the hell are you!?
Come on, you've got to get it!
What!?
All right, let's all work together!
One at a time!
Why can't I hit that blue thing!?
I'm not gonna be some brat's souvenir.
Got it!
Congratulations!
Huh?
It's gone.
I can't find it.
Huh? I saw it fall.
We all saw it!
Man, that sucked.
At least I'm safe now...
And that's what happened.
And you've been running around all this time after the posters got taken down?
No one would come otherwise!
Well, at least you're optimistic.
Even if they hadn't been taken down, you were getting too excited about a nursery school's bazaar.
If this was going to happen, I probably shouldn't have even suggested it.
Nah, once you've decided on something it's important to go through with it.
Even if things get messed up, you can't just quit.
Yeah...
Even if you're sopping wet, even if you're ambushed by a sniper...
O... kay?
Er, never mind.
Don't get too disappointed just because there aren't any customers.
Welcome back, Kobato!
You're late!
Look how much we sold!
The teru-teru bouzu sold too!
You showed me some real bargains.
How long are you just gonna stand there?
Sorry!
We don't have enough people to handle this many customers.
You need to help out.
Okay!
Kobato!
Thanks. We only have this many customers because you tried so hard.
I didn't really-
Look.
They look like they're having fun.
It's all thanks to you, Kobato.
Kobato.
Domoto! Thanks for coming!
You're welcome.
I had a lot of fun.
That's great!
But I really wanted to buy something from you.
Really? I made things!
I wonder what happened to them?
They didn't sell...
Of course. Who would want some mysterious life-form where they can't even tell whether it's a chicken, a penguin, or a sheep?
How about I buy one?
Really!?
Thank you!
It's really, really you, Kobato.
What is it, a bunny?
Domoto!
This was such a wonderful day!
Sucked for me.
Really?
Yeah! Weren't you listening to me!?
Well...
Yeah, I guess.
You don't just guess!
Oh well, as long as I still have that, all's well that ends well.
I'll scarf it down as soon as I get home! No, wait, I'll savor it.
That?
That.
What is it?
Huh?
My baumkuchen's gone!
Looks like I'm gonna have to go back to the nursery and get it.
Oh, right, the baumkuchen. That sold right away.
What the hell did you do!?
You said you were going to get something that wass sure to sell. That was the baumkuchen, right?
Thanks a ton!
Your score for today is 80 points for your enthusiasm about the bazaar, and...
a total of -300 for my disappointment!
Why, Ioryogi!? Are you disappointed because of me? I'm sorry!
You can't apologize it away!
Then I'll cheer you up by giving you one of my cute bunnies!
I don't need one of those!
What if I throw a second one in?
Knock it off!
How about this cute bear and sheep?
I can't even tell which is which! They're all mysterious life-forms!
You're terrible, Ioryogi!
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
... Warmth in a Chill Wind.
Next episode